<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon  Omega Version.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Omega Ruby Version</name>
                <desc>Pokemon ruby with mega evolutions</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon  Omega Version-image.jpg</image>
                <rating>0.7</rating>
                <releasedate>20040129T000000</releasedate>
                <developer>Game Freak</developer>
                <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
                <genre>Adventure</genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon (Old) White.gba</path>
                <name>Pokémon White</name>
                <desc>You are a student and studied at West Academy to learn about Pokemon Art. To graduate, you must receive a Pokemon from the Professor and train it then you will be challenged by a mysterious trainer. After all, you receive a request from Professor Oak to collect and complete his Pokedex about Pokemon Data. So you start your journey around Denta to do this request. Along your way, you meet other trainers, catch Pokemon but you also need to stop Team Aqua’s plans. They are an evil team and planning to catch Celebi to use his powers to be the owner of this region. That’s how your game starts.
                Features

                New World Map of Denta Region
                Moves from Pokemon Diamond/Pearl
                New Trainer Battle Themes
                West Academy
                </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon_Old_White_01.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Adamantite.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Adamantite</name>
                <desc>You sleep and have a special dream that Dialga, Palkia and Giratina are fighting together. Outside of the battle, Darkrai, Cresselia and other Legendaries are watching. But suddenly, you wake up and see you are ready for the new trip with a lot of dangerous campaign. You must find your Pokemon Starter and begin the trip. Also, find out why you have a special dream.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Adamantite-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Advance Adventure.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Advance Adventure</name>
                <desc>You are the child of the poorest family in town. You have no friends and you are bullied constantly due to your economic status. Though you are poor and have no hope of every becoming a Pokemon trainer, you still dream about it.
                        One morning you wake up, and surprisingly the Pokemon professor wants to see you. Apparently, his grandson suddenly took a change of events in his life and has taken over the Pokemon Headquarters. You are told to stop him and his 8 subordinates across the region. You will quest to stop the unjust ruler by defeating his 8 subordinates, the 8 genetically modified tyrant pokemon running wild in towns and infiltrating the Pokemon Headquarters.

                Features
                        new region
                        all pokemon are catchable
                        no trade eveolutions
                        all tm's obtainable
                        gen 5
                        after game storyline</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Advance Adventure-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Armageddon.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Armageddon</name>
                <desc>Giovani and his Team Rocket have a research to make a Time Machine. When Giovani has it, he goes back to the past and does many bad things. He prevents Professor Oak to study then he destroys Elite Four existence. Then he goes to another world to capture all Pokemon Legendaries and Pokemon from the best Trainers. You are one of the best trainers after Ash and Lance so your Pokemon were captured by him. You are so angry and want to find out what happened. That is how your journey begins.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Armageddon-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Ash Gray.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Ash Gray</name>
                <desc>Your name is Ash Ketchum and you're about to embark on your big Pokémon adventure. Unfortunately, you stayed up all night watching Pokémon battles and woke up late! With all your rivals from Pallet Town (the most annoying being Gary) having taken all the starters available, it looks like you'll just have to go home ... unless you want Pikachu instead.

                        You're about to embark on an adventure of 116 events (plus two movie events) that will put you in Ash's shoes, allow you to catch the Pokémon he catches, and make the decisions he makes. How will your journey as Ash Ketchum play out? There's only one way to find out!

            Follows the same events as in the Pokemon Anime series
            Catch all of the Pokémon Ash does
            Be rewarded for carrying Ash's team
            New Tiles, Sprites and Maps
            New Tools to replace HMs-
            Hatchet replaces Cut
            Computer Teleport System replaces Fly
            Raft replaces Surf
            Pickaxe replaces Rock Smash
            Climb Kit is used instead of Rock Climb
            Whirlpuller is used to cross whirlpools
                </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Ash Gray-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Ash's Quest.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Ash's Quest</name>
                <desc>Pokemon Ash’s Quest is an unofficial ROM hack based on the original Pokemon Fire Red Version. Initially released back in 2009, the game aims to include all the important events from the first 82 episodes of the original Pokemon anime series including the singing Jigglypuff, the Pokemon League tournament, the banned episodes, and more. What makes this ROM hack different from the others, is that this ROM does not contain any random trainer or wild Pokemon as it stays true to the anime series</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Ash's Quest-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Azure Horizons.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Azure Horizons</name>
                <desc>After months of waiting, you finally get your acceptance letter to the regional league. Finally the chance to follow in the footsteps of your brother, a great Pokémon trainer. With goal set, you begin to start your journey as a Pokémon trainer growing with each challenge. Working your way through the ranks and eventually, to the top. However, as soon as your journey begins something has happened. A disturbance has undergone, strange Pokémon trainers have been going around the region causing havoc. Their goal, however, is out of the ordinary. What it is currently is completely unknown... will it conflict with your own? Along the way you will meet people who can either aid or hinder you on your quest. There is more to them then you first thought, however. </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Azure Horizons-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Black Orb.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Black Orb</name>
                <desc>Even since you are a kid, you shows the excellent skills in Pokemon. It can be explained because you are the son of a famous Pokemon scientist. Your Dad makes the researches about the mystery orb that may be a key to activate a very very big thing. That thing is also what Team Zen concerns because it has the strong powers to destroy the world. Your Dad doesn’t know that his researches are helping to Team Zen. One day, you know these things and your missions are to stop Team Zen. In Pokemon Black Orb, you will decide your own destiny.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Black Orb-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Crono.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Crono</name>
                <desc>You live in a small house in Midamond region. You have a dream. You meet a dark power person. His name is Crono. You wonder who is Crono? And your trip is to find the answer.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Crono-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Dark Cobalt.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Dark Cobalt</name>
                <desc>The history of this region was associated with Entei, Raikou and Suicune – three Pokemon Legendaries known as Beasts. They own the very great powers to change the worldsuch as Molten Garnet, Arctic Lapis-Lazuli and Charged Topaz. Nowadays, they are hiding and no one can know where they are. Team Aura, the Evil Team, always wants to be the owner of the Pokemon World so they will not miss this opportunity.

                        You will be an important person that will save Felith from the bad guys. It maybe your destiny. You decide to have an adventure around this region after your elder brother won Felith Pokemon League. You want to win the same title like your brother but you must destroy Team Auras plans before you can do that. Good luck!!!</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Dark Cobalt-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Emerald Mod.gba</path>
                <name>Pokémon Emerald Version - modded</name>
                <desc>The Hoenn region is unstable--Rayquaza has awakened! Your skills as a Trainer will be challenged like they've never been challenged before as you try to maintain the balance between Kyogre &amp; Groudon. Prove your skills by earning badges &amp; gaining access to Battle Frontier - the front line of Pokémon battling that offers a whole new level of competition. Never-before-experienced battles await you!
• The third adventure with new episodes in the Hoenn region!
• Tons of new features, including surprising plot twists and changes to where and how often you can catch certain Pokémon!
• Use the Game Boy Advance Wireless Adapter to trade &amp; battle between Pokémon Emerald and Pokémon FireRed and LeafGreen versions.
• Expand your collection when you trade with a friend. Using a Game Link cable, link up with Pokémon Ruby &amp; Sapphire, Pokémon FireRed &amp; LeafGreen or Pokémon Colosseum to catch them all!</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Emerald Mod-image.jpg</image>
                <rating>0.6</rating>
                <releasedate>20040916T000000</releasedate>
                <developer>Game Freak</developer>
                <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
                <genre>Adventure</genre>
                <players>4+</players>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Flora Sky.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Flora Sky</name>
                <desc>You'll come to a land with many mysteries of the legendary Pokemon. After the battle between Dialga and Palkia, the portal between Torn World - the world of Giratina and real world is opened. Giratina appears and brings many unanticapated dangers. And you must close this portal before its too late. Meanwhile, Team Magma and Aqua are seeking the legendary Fire and Water type Pokemon to dominate their world. Together with other friends, our hero will prevent the heat of the legendary Pokemon by the actions of Team Magma and Aqua. What will help Groudon and Kyogre calm down? For more stories, let's play.. </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Flora Sky-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Glacier Version.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Glacier Version</name>
                <desc>You, our protagonist… are a ten years old trainer boy. You are living with your mom and brother in the quiet and peaceful Sunray Town. Usually, this town is filled with sun light and its warming so everybody can work and live happily. But that time won’t last long. These recent days, the whole region – including Sunray Town – is being covered in snow and ice. People get cold everyday. They have never seen such a cold like this. When seeing this, you cannot just stand there and endure the cold… so you go to meet Professor Kirk. He is the brother of Professor Birch and his Pokemon knowledge is also great as his brother. Kirk tells you that the legendary Regice is using its special power and he doesn’t know why is it doing this. You immediately prepare everything and go to find the reason for many answers. On your way, you will confront several opponents – get items – interact with people – defeat all the gym leaders to get their badges anda finally the title Pokemon Champion. Finally, you will now that Team Glacier is behind all of these things. What are you waiting for? Come and get them!</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Glacier Version-image.png</image>
                <rating>0.7</rating>
                <releasedate>20040129T000000</releasedate>
                <developer>Game Freak</developer>
                <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
                <genre>Adventure</genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Legend Of Dragons.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Legend of dragons</name>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Legend Of Dragons-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Light Platinum Complete.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Light Platinum</name>
                <desc>Pokemon Light Platinum is really excellent Remake ROM from Pokemon Ruby Version. Many new features were included in the completed version and some Pokemon Generation 4th are available.
                        Included New Region ZHERY
                        Included New Leaders and Elite Four
                        Included New Rivals
                        Pokémons of all Regions (Johto, Kanto, Hoen, Sinnoh)
                        You can have trips to another areas
                        Can catch all Pokemons Legendaries
                        Included All New sprites
                        Included All New events
                        Included All New Tiles
                        New Final Event: Pokemon World Championship</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Light Platinum Complete-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Liquid Crystal.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Liquid Crystal</name>
                <desc>full gbc crystal remake with new regions and a bunch of new mechanics and features</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Liquid Crystal-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Marble.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Marble</name>
                <desc>Your region now is GARNA and it is in Lowheaven. Everyone in this area knows the adventure of Ran and J.Akira. 20 years after that adventure, a new journey was made by a young trainer – it is you. You need to raise your Pokemon Level up, challenge with the best GYM Leaders. Then you have to protect everyone and save the world from the mafia. With the help from Professor Baro, you can do that.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Marble-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Quartz.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Quartz</name>
                <desc>The story begins with the player riding in a moving van with Professor Baro (who replaces Professor Birch's role in Pokémon Ruby, Sapphire, and Emerald Versions). The player and his mother have just moved in to Breeze Town of the Corna region, which is a heavily modified Hoenn region. Coincidentially, the player's rival and his/her mother have moved in to the next-door house around the same time. Upon meeting the rival, he/she immediately develops a crush on the player while doing a poor job at hiding it. </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Quartz-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Rijon Adventures.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Rijon Adventures</name>
                <desc>The game is similiar to Pokémon FireRed, except that the player takes control of Brown's child and not Brown himself, Prof. Oak is replaced by the aunt of the player's rival, probably Mura's sister/cousin

                        Keep in mind, that only Brown himself is the parent that apears in the house, the Protagonist's mom is not seen

                        In addition, the NES in the player's room is replaced by a WII </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Rijon Adventures-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Life Of Guardians.gba</path>
                <name>Pokémon Ruby Destiny; Life of Guardians</name>
                <desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Ruby. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Life Of Guardians-image.jpg</image>
                <rating>0.6</rating>
                <releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
                <developer>Game Freak</developer>
                <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
                <genre>Adventure</genre>
                <players>4+</players>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Reign Of Legends.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Reign Of Legends.gba</name>
                <desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Ruby. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Reign Of Legends-image.jpg</image>
                <rating>0.6</rating>
                <releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
                <developer>Game Freak</developer>
                <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
                <genre>Adventure</genre>
                <players>4+</players>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Rescue Rangers.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Rescue Rangers.gba</name>
                <desc>The race to catch 'em all is on again in Pokemon Ruby. This entry in the Pokemon series features an all-new storyline, awesome new Pokemon, and addictive RPG gameplay. One of the biggest additions to Pokemon Ruby is the two-on-two battle system, which allows you to link up with three friends to battle competitively or cooperatively. You can also showcase your Pokemon's coolness, beauty, cuteness, smartness, and toughness in Pokemon contests. With new Pokemon, two-on-two battles, and an all-new region of Hoenn to explore, Pokemon Sapphire takes the Pokemon experience to the next level.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Ruby Destiny - Rescue Rangers-image.jpg</image>
                <rating>0.6</rating>
                <releasedate>20021121T000000</releasedate>
                <developer>Game Freak</developer>
                <publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
                <genre>Adventure</genre>
                <players>4+</players>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Septo Conquest.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Septo Conquest</name>
                <desc>One year ago, the King of Septo was assassinated and his kingdom was stolen from him by two people known as The Dictators. Prof. Oak, who was working as the King's chief researcher, managed to rescue the King's only child and took him/her to his hometown of Faris Town.

                        Now living with an alcholic foster mother, you, the only child to the King and the true heir to the throne of the Septo Region, must take the region back. After Oak gives you a Pokemon, you start your very own quest. The objective is to overthrow the seven Barons (minions of the Dictators), each of who rule one island. By doing that, you'll be able to conquer that island and get closer to the showdown with the two Dictators.

                        However, there is more to it. You will also be fighting two evil teams: Team Vine and Team Solar. Team Vine are a bunch of eco-warriors who fight the save nature, but in bad ways, and Team Solar are an organisation of criminals who steal, pillage and kidnap people and Pokemon alike. </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Septo Conquest-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Sienna.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Sienna</name>
                <desc>The day has finally come, the day for your era to begin. After months of waiting, you hear of an opening at the Indigo Plateau trainer school in Kanto. After sending off your letter, your CV is rejected. Mostly because of your lack of experience; but, your alternative is to go out on your own journey. Challenging the gyms, and finally the plateau, in Kanto, should be no problem. But, the region is being disturbed by the up-rising of a mysterious team. This ‘team’ have been going around the region and causing havoc, stealing Pokémon and mugging shops. Will you merge in with the group, let them be, or will you stop them on your journey? It’s all up to you!</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Sienna-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Snakewood.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Snakewood</name>
                <desc>Pokémon Snakewood is a hacked ROM of Pokémon Ruby, created by ROM hacker Cutlerine. The game is set a few years after the events of Ruby, and you play as the younger brother or sister of Ruby's protagonist (called Landon in this game). The game takes place in a post-zombie apocalyptic Hoenn region, where the hero must fight his/her way through the decaying region to restore order. </desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Snakewood-image.png</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
        <game>
                <path>./Pokemon Uranium.gba</path>
                <name>Pokemon Uranium</name>
                <desc>Pokémon Uranium is a fan-made game based on the Pokémon series. The game was in development for nine years, and used the RPG Maker XP engine. The game adds 150 new fan-made species of Pokémon, along with a new region. Similar to the official games, Uranium contains both online trading and online battling.</desc>
                <image>/home/pi/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/pokemonhacks/Pokemon Uranium-image.jpg</image>
                <releasedate>20040927T000000</releasedate>
                <developer></developer>
                <publisher></publisher>
                <genre></genre>
        </game>
</gameList>
